southafrica.to 2012-12-24

# SouthAfrica.TO privacy policy

1 Aug 2009. At SouthAfrica.TO (South Africa Travel Online) we recognize that privacy is important to you. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use SouthAfrica.TO's services.

#### **Personal Information we collect**

  * SouthAfrica.TO collects personal information when you utilise its services or voluntarily provide such information. SouthAfrica.TO may merge personal information collected from you with information from other SouthAfrica.TO services.

  * SouthAfrica.TO may use technologies (such as cookies) to learn about how you use SouthAfrica.TO services in order to improve the quality of its services.

  * SouthAfrica.TO's servers automatically record information when you visit its website or use some of its products - including the IP address, URL, language, browser type and the date and time of your visit and requests. 

#### **Uses** of information collected 

  * SouthAfrica.TO processes personal data on its servers in whichever country they are based (e.g the USA).

  * SouthAfrica.TO may use personal information to provide services, including services that display customized content and advertising. 

  * SouthAfrica.TO may also use personal information to operate and improve SouthAfrica.TO technologies and services. 

  * SouthAfrica.TO may use third parties to assist in the processing your personal information.

  * SouthAfrica.TO may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of SouthAfrica.TO. 

  * SouthAfrica.TO may share information with third parties in limited circumstances.

#### **Your privacy choices**

You may decline to visit www.southafrica.to, you may decline to to provide personal information to SouthAfrica.TO and you may refuse cookies in your browser; it is possible that some of SouthAfrica.TO's features wont work as a result.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy 

SouthAfrica.TO may update this policy.

#### **More privacy policy information**

If you have further queries relating to SouthAfrica.TO's privacy policy, please contact us [](http://www.google.com/support/bin/request.py?contact_type=privacy)at cheapflights@southafrica.to
